(Penny:)Oh, no.
We were gonna hang out. Let's hang out.
- It's cool. Go back to Kevin.
- No, he had to leave.
(Leonard:)Interesting.
(Leonard:)So now that he's gone,
you wanna hang out with me.
- This must be Penny.
- Yep.
(Woman:)I totally get it.
- Uh, I'm sorry. Get what?
- Don't worry about it.
There's guys over there.
Go talk to them.
- No, no. I wanna know what you told her.
- That's kind of between me and...
- Laura.
(Penny:)Oh, okay, I see.
So while he was telling you things...
(Penny:)...did he mention he owns not one,
but two Star Trek uniforms?
- Really?
- Yeah. Wears them.
(Penny:)Not just for Halloween.
(Leonard:)Hey, pal.
(Leonard:)You didn't see me telling Kevin
that you thought cold wars...
(Leonard:)...were only fought in winter.
Okay, then I'll return the favor...
(Penny:)- ...and I won't tell...
- Laura.
...Laura that haIf the dirty movies
you own are animated.